Hi, I'm back and so is a cupful of my urine.
I've produced approximately 65 ml of urine sample; 60 ml is the limit.
As you can see, one of the dots is so warm that it has gone blue, which is going to be a detection past green.
I assure you with 100% of my heart, soul and being that this is a freshly produced unadulterated urine sample of my own creation.
So now, we are going to crack open the test strip and we are going to execute our test.
Now, this is a timed test so it is important that you have a watch, clock or other timing device available.
I showed the test strip to you earlier, but I'll show it to you again.
What we are going to do is simply place this in the cup, up to the max urine level.
So, this is going to be the minimum line here and the max line is here.
These are your result strips.
You are not going to want to contaminate these with urine, nor are you going to want to touch any of this with your bare hand.
It can possibly introduce agents, skin oils or other contaminants that can skew your test results.
It's going to stay in for approximately 10 minutes and then we have approximately a 5 minute window to read it.
So, let's go ahead and dip it in and check.
We are going to come back in 10 minutes and take a look at any sort of intoxicants or other drugs that may or, most likely, may not be in my urine.